http://www.kclu.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
At KCLU, we recognize the importance of privacy. This privacy policy explains how information that KCLU receives or gathers from you may be used, how you may request that your data be corrected or how to opt-out from future communications from KCLU and the efforts we make to protect your privacy. Gathering of Information KCLU collects personally-identifying information (such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number and/or credit card information) from the KCLU Web site only if you choose to provide that information to us. KCLU asks visitors to provide certain personal information under various circumstances, including but not limited to when they make a donation to KCLU and when they register for any online contests/giveaways. Like all other Web servers, KCLU's Web server automatically creates log files for each visitor who accesses our site. These "access logs" allow us to make our site more useful to our visitors. The access logs do NOT record a visitor's name, address, phone number, credit card numbers, or any other personally-identifiable information. Rather, they contain some or all of the following information: The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of the machine which accessed our Web site. The date of the visit. The time of the visit. The path taken through our Web site. The type of computer and browser being used. A list of files downloaded or viewed. The amount of time spent listening to audio or video files. Any errors encountered. Cookies KCLU may use 'cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a string of characters that can be written to a file on the user's computer system when the user visits a Web site. Only the Web site that set the cookie can read it, and it can only be used as a record keeping device to store information that the site already has. It cannot, for example, be used to read other information from the user's hard drive. KCLU uses cookies to track users' activity through the site in order to improve the site's architecture, to offer the user interactive features that would not be possible without them, and to recall specific information to save the user time during subsequent visits to the site. Our sponsorship service vendors, which serve sponsorship messages onto our site, and vendors that measure the use of KCLU.org, may also use their own cookies. If you wish to prevent certain or all cookies from being set to your computer system you may disable them in your browser's preferences, although some web site features on KCLU.org may then not function correctly, or at all. Use of Information
Personally-identifiable information is used as follows: responding to user e-mails; listing name and location (city, state and/or country) information provided by users when publishing user e-mails or other submissions; fulfillment of orders for goods or services; fulfillment of donations to KCLU; contest management; editorial purposes such as contacting users for an online survey; sending communications, including marketing and promotional communications, from KCLU to users who have 'opted in' to the receipt of such communications; other similar internal KCLU purposes; and other purposes specified at the time the information is gathered. Donor Privacy
KCLU’s long established policy is to never sell, rent, exchange or give KCLU's donor list to any other organization. This policy is consistent with our belief that our donors have placed their financial trust in KCLU. We appreciate and respect their trust. We will safeguard KCLU's donor list so that it will remain confidential. Website User Privacy
KCLU does not sell, rent, loan, or exchange personally-identifiable information about users of the KCLU.org web site with third parties. KCLU service vendors (for example, the company that manages our e-mail newsletter distribution process) may receive personally-identifiable information from us only for the purpose of providing services to KCLU. If a third-party service vendor to KCLU receives any personally-identifiable information from us, they receive it subject to the same restrictions we apply – that is, they may not sell, rent, loan, or exchange that information, and may only use or transmit some or all of the information for the purpose of providing services to KCLU. KCLU also may disclose personally-identifiable information if we are required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with legal process, (b) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the KCLU Web site, or (c) protect the personal safety or property of KCLU Web site users, KCLU and its employees, or members of the public. KCLU uses non-identifying aggregate information to analyze use of and better design the KCLU Web site and to share with third parties in aggregate form only as appropriate. However, we will not disclose any information that could be used to identify those users. Submissions
If you send an e-mail, story idea, essay and/or other submission ("Submission") to KCLU through our Web site, we may print that Submission, or an excerpt from it, on the KCLU Web site, read it on air, or otherwise publish it in any other medium, together with your name and location (city, state and/or country) if you provide that information to us. Opt out
If you do not want your personally-identifying information to be collected or used for any of these purposes, you can simply 'opt out' according to the process described below. Security
KCLU has in place what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Some sections of the KCLU Web Sites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and other technologies to encrypt information while it is in transmission between the KCLU Web Sites servers and the user's computer or mobile device. Some information, including financial information, provided by visitors to the KCLU Web Sites is additionally encrypted if it will be stored by KCLU. Personally-identifiable financial information that we collect is deleted from storage as soon as it is no longer needed to complete a donation or other transaction. Children
Persons under the age of 13 are not authorized to use KCLU Web Sites. If we discover that we have collected any personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will remove that information from our databases as soon as possible. Persons under the age of 18 are not authorized to provide any personally-identifying information on KCLU Web Sites, including participating in KCLU contests. Corrections to Personal Data; Opting Out
Please contact us via e-mail or by telephoning +1.805.493.3900 to a) correct or update any personal information in KCLU databases that you believe is in error, b) opt-out of future communications from KCLU or c) request KCLU to make reasonable efforts to remove your personal information from KCLU databases. The user understands that it may be impossible to delete all personally-identifiable information entirely because of backups and records of deletions. Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms KCLU reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of the KCLU Web site constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. Please make sure that you read KCLU's Terms of Use to understand additional terms and conditions which apply to the use of our Web site. If you have any questions or comments concerning out privacy policy, please contact us via email, telephone (805) 493-3900 or send a letter to:KCLU60 W. Olsen Rd. #4400Thousand Oaks, CA 91360USA Links to other Sites
It is important to note that the KCLU Web site contains links to other sites that may not follow the same privacy policies as the KCLU Web site. For instance, clicking on a sponsorship notice on KCLU.org will take you to an entirely different site. These sites may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that KCLU.org would not. KCLU is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites. Please visit these sites if you wish to review their privacy policies. Updated September 27, 2016
